<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TMyMoney Documentation</title>
    <link>https://davidgma.github.io/tmymoney/</link>
    <description>Recent content on TMyMoney Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 17:12:02 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://davidgma.github.io/tmymoney/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Overview</title>
      <link>https://davidgma.github.io/tmymoney/architecture/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 16:38:48 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidgma.github.io/tmymoney/architecture/overview/</guid>
      <description>Architecture and Set-up While KMyMoney can be installed and used without much technical knowledge, I don&amp;rsquo;t think this will ever be the case for TMyMoney. It runs in a terminal, it uses node, you need to be able to configure a web server with SSL and authentication if you want to use over the internet. Setting up a free Google Cloud Platform VM is a good idea too.
This is the architecture of the application and the tools I used in building it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Node</title>
      <link>https://davidgma.github.io/tmymoney/architecture/node/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 12:18:08 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidgma.github.io/tmymoney/architecture/node/</guid>
      <description>I installed Node using the Node Version Manager.
You can install it with apt too but this doesn&amp;rsquo;t give such a recent version. After installing it per the instructions I installed the latest LTS version of Node.
bash command -v nvm nvm ls-remote nvm install --lts node --version which node which npm  The which commands should give paths that are under the directory ~/.nvm rather than under /usr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Typescript</title>
      <link>https://davidgma.github.io/tmymoney/architecture/language/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 11:07:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidgma.github.io/tmymoney/architecture/language/</guid>
      <description>I used Typescript.
npm install -g typescript  Inside a node project (created later), you will need the node types.
npm install --save @types/node  A useful place to look for other types (for other npm packages you may want to use) is Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s TypeSearch page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angular</title>
      <link>https://davidgma.github.io/tmymoney/architecture/angular/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 12:36:47 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidgma.github.io/tmymoney/architecture/angular/</guid>
      <description>I used Angular] for the web client. Angular produces static web sites - a web site where all the code is served once by the web server and then doesn&amp;rsquo;t need to be served again for the entire running of the web app by the user, unless the user refreshes the web page. The advantage of this is that it&amp;rsquo;s cheaper to serve and a lot of companies now offer free serving of static websites, such as Github with Github Pages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git</title>
      <link>https://davidgma.github.io/tmymoney/architecture/git/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 12:49:09 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidgma.github.io/tmymoney/architecture/git/</guid>
      <description>Git is needed for version control and for safely storing code on Github.
I used the Ubuntu packaged version of git.
sudo apt update sudo apt install git git --version  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo</title>
      <link>https://davidgma.github.io/tmymoney/architecture/hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 17:12:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidgma.github.io/tmymoney/architecture/hugo/</guid>
      <description>The documentation is created using Hugo with the theme learn.
Installation of Hugo:
snap install hugo --channel=extended hugo version  The documentation is written in the subdirectory of the project doc. From the main project folder (tmymoney):
hugo new site doc  Then install the theme:
cd doc cd themes hugo mod init https://github.com/matcornic/hugo-theme-learn.git hugo mod get -u git clone https://github.com/matcornic/hugo-theme-learn.git  Note that some of the theme isn&amp;rsquo;t stored by git, so after cloning the project to another computer, you need to re-do the above step.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>